Nukumizu Kazuhiko
Nu
Huh?
Wait a minute, Yuki!
I don't think I'm ready for this yet!
S-Senpai, why are you here?
Then how do you want me to do it, Hayato?
There's no way I'm making my sleepy
Komari-chan go to school by herself.
Just shove it in there? Like this?
Ow!
Oh, it might be too tight.
I guess it's bigger than it looks.
Not bad, huh? This is one that
I save for very special occasions.
You have such a big ring finger, Hayato.
I-I told you I'm a size 14!
S-Senpai...
Now, just hold still for me, okay?
Don't put it in!
T-Turn the volume down!
Love
Tsuwabuki
Fest
Student Council Office
Excuse me.
Wh-What do you want?
Tiara-chan.
Say the word.
"Meow." Say it.
S-Senpai, even as an order,
that's a little too...
This is the student council office, right?
You're refusing the chairwoman's request?
Never!
All right, I'll do it!
"Meow."
Here I go.
Meow!
S-So... what can I help you with... meow?
Oh, uh, here's a picture
of our completed exhibit.
All right. We have officially received it.
Tiara-chan.
We've officially received it, meow!
What am I being exposed to here?
Edible
Readings
Y-You're late, Nukumizu.
You sure got here early today.
T-Tsukinoki-senpai picked me up.
N-Nukumizu.
Um, well...
Th-Thank you.
Y-You turned everything I wrote
into a r-really nice display.
This was all Asagumo-san's...
Uh, I mean, you should thank
Yakishio's friend for it.
Nakagawa
Rieko
She's the one who did the layout.
R-Really?
But you printed it out so nicely...
My friend and President Tamaki
helped with that. Impressive, huh?
Th-Then what about the room decorations?
Those were Tsukinoki-senpai's idea.
All those guys were roped in
to help by Yanami-san and Ya—
L-Let me compliment you on something.
What's this? You want to compliment my work?
Very well. Don't hold back.
Shower me with compliments.
D-Drop dead.
Yanami-san said she has some free time
this afternoon and can take over for a while.
O-Our senpai said they'll come
after their assembly, too.
Yeah, that's right.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
This is the Tsuwabuki
High School student council.
We are expecting a number of guests
from outside today, so please remember
that each and every one of you represents
Tsuwabuki, and don't do anything
that may tarnish our reputation.
So without further ado,
the 98th Tsuwabuki Fest is open.
Yay!
Th-That little kid said he read
the picture book reports.
And he even bought a pancake, huh?
Um...
Hi. If you collect all the
stamps, you get a treat.
Okay!
I guess I find it easier to talk to
people who aren't my own age.
A collaboration between literary works
and food? That's an interesting concept.
I'm taking a look.
Uh, sure.
Is this an inspection?
You do get right to the point.
You may view it that way if you like.
This is a well-made exhibit.
However...
The lit club has been in trouble
countless times in the past.
The next time something happens...
Will we be dissolved?
Dissolution...
may be a little too severe.
Huh?
How about something like
a temporary dissolution?
Um, what's a temporary dissolution?
I'm not exactly sure, but I guess if you get
temporarily dissolved three times, you're out.
But I'm not exactly sure.
She seems pretty eccentric, too.
Chairwoman, we're on a very
tight inspection schedule, meow!
M-M-Meow?!
Wh-What in the world are you
doing in a place like this, meow?
Um, this is the literature club's exhibit.
Huh? It is, meow?
In that case, please excuse me, meow.
I'll be on my way now.
Oh, and also, Chairwoman, when will
you be changing into costume, meow?
I don't intend to.
Meow?!
B-But Shikiya-senpai said you were
going to dress up as a prince, meow!
Splendid... exhibit.
Senpai, have you been lying
to the vice chairwoman?
Tiara-chan is... cute and gullible.
And now, you are also a vampire!
We are finally of the same kind, darling!
Let's get married!
What's up?
Has Amanatsu-sensei been bullying you?
Sh-She said something to me.
Well, that is a calamity.
Oh, Nukumizu!
These peanut things are really tasty!
Did you make them yourself?
No, my little sister did.
Uh-huh...
Nukumizu, does your little sister
have a big brother?
Uh, that would be me.
No, not you.
Someone around 30 with
a steady job would be ideal.
Uh, the next time I see my relatives,
I'll ask if they can think of anyone.
Oh, how sweet. When Konami finds
her ideal man, I'd sure like to ride...
I mean, I'd sure like to meet him.
I'll never let you near him, Konuki-chan!
And you'll have to watch
the wedding remotely!
This is such a bad influence on the kids.
I wish they'd hurry up and leave.
How about from behind frosted glass?
Sure, that works.
Hurray!
That last one was well-done.
S-Something's coming.
How's it go-oooh-ing?
Nice to see you, Yanami-san.
Oh, you do have guests!
Your costume's a little dirty. Is it okay?
Yeah, it's chocolate.
The kids who come over to see me
all have chocolate on their hands,
or bits of candy stuck around their mouths.
I don't know why,
but that kind of makes sense.
I'll watch the shop for a while,
so you guys go take a break.
Okay, thanks. Back in a bit.
One more thing. Don't you dare
set foot in the clubroom, okay?
B-But I have a book I need to finish.
Then I shall burn it.
Then where are we supposed to go?
You are both going to go
and enjoy the festival.
B-But I don't really want to—
As a girl in a literature club,
you at least need a boy or two to dote on you.
I know this is Nukumizu-kun we're talking
about, but he's still a boy. Right?
U-Um, Nukumizu.
Hmm?
S-Someone in the classroom just now told
me they wanted time to read the reports,
and asked if they could
take pictures of them.
Really? That's great.
Yeah.
Where should we go after we eat?
I d-don't care. Anywhere you want is fine.
Here. Open wide.
Mmm! It's so good!
If you didn't know any better, it could look
like there was something between us.
I'd prefer to avoid such a misunderstanding.
Komari. I have a suggestion to make.
As an experiment, would you mind
calling me "big brother"?
H-Have you gone totally nuts?
No, wait. I don't mean anything weird by it.
But when we're eating together like this,
it almost looks like we're here on a date.
Then again, when they see a girl choking on
udon, they might not assume that after all.
Choco Cigarettes
Jackpot!
I made it myself. It can shoot holes
in a soda can quite easily.
This is a deadly weapon.
Um, I brought Komari from my club with me.
Oh!
Hey, Komari!
You're that Komari-san? The reports you
wrote for the exhibit were wonderful!
Huh? U-Uh, well, thank you
very much for your help.
Not at all! I found it fascinating!
I was especially enthralled by how it so
skillfully aligned male social camaraderie
with structures of romantic engagement.
You must be a tremendous
fujoshi, Komari-san.
I don't have any other fujoshi friends,
so I must say I'm absolutely intrigued!
Please, when you have a moment,
tell me all of your favorite BL works!
I got a message from Yakishio.
What do you think?
Wanna say hi before we go back?
Th-There are too many people outside.
Okay, I'll go say hi to her by myself.
Yakishio.
Oh, it's Nuk-kun!
Wh-What the heck are you wearing?
Get this. Right now,
I'm dressed as Track and Mask!
And here is the menu
of available challenges.
Masked Challenger
"Face Lady Track and Mask in
a no-handicap 100-meter race."
Um, I think I'll pass on that one.
Then why don't I challenge you instead?
Whoa, Tako-bo? Long time no see!
Remember? We were both sprinters on the track
team in middle school. Takahashi the slacker!
Why the heck would I know him?
So are you still running track?
Yeah, I've been training tons recently.
I'm sure I can beat your 100-meter time now.
All right! So you're gonna challenge me?
That's why I'm here.
However...
If I win, will you go see a movie with me?
A movie with Tako-bo?
Yeah. Okay.
So we're on for a 1,500-meter race.
Huh? Not the 100-meter?
Well, you're faster than me
on the 100-meter, right?
Yeah, but I...
Shoelaces done up? All warmed up?
Okay, on your marks...
Wait!
Masked Challenger
Get set... Go!
Poor guy's gonna be traumatized.
The next one's in the courtyard!
Wait for me!
Princess Anna, I love you!
Don't die! Please don't die!
Princess Anna!
How can a ghost die? What a crappy script.
There's my big brother.
Don't you want to talk to him?
I can only capture his natural behavior
if I remain hidden like this.
It's so cute!
Aren't you lucky?
Yeah! Can I eat it?
When we get home.
Aw...
Oh, Nukumizu. Been waiting for you.
H-Hurry up and help.
Hey, there was a lot going on.
Like a lost love, and a ghost's re-death scene.
D-Do you need some help?
I want one of those.
Picture books contain tales of friendship,
compassion, and all the elements of adventure!
Even someone as open to
radical possibilities as myself
could not possibly adapt them!
I wonder if I should stop her.
I'm really grateful, Nukumizu. Koto and I
couldn't have pulled this off ourselves.
Edible Readings
Thank you very much.
Uh, ah, yeah, um...
Komari put everything she had into it.
Thanks, everyone.
Edible
Readings
The literature club's exhibit,
"Edible Readings," had a total of 117 visitors.
We sold 40 treats and
14 copies of our newsletter.
I couldn't have ended my
presidency with a better event.
And it's all thanks to you guys.
Shintaro, are you okay?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
It is 4 PM. The 98th Tsuwabuki
Fest has now concluded.
I guess this means you two have
"graduated" from the club now.
That makes me a little sad.
Well, that's a nice thing to say.
But I bet you're really thinking,
"Good riddance!" aren't you?
Polite conversation greases
the wheels of society.
You've become a pretty
smooth talker, Nukumizu-kun.
I think Komari's feeling some pressure
over becoming the club president.
I'm sure she is.
There's already a presidents' meeting
coming up next weekend.
People will be giving self-introductions
and club activity reports.
Do you think you could help
support her for just a little bit longer?
I wish I could.
But that's your role now, Nukumizu-kun.
I don't mean it in a romantic way,
but you're the only one
who can stand by her side.
That's how it is now.
I don't really know... but it feels like
Komari doesn't let me get too involved.
Are you sure? I think Komari-chan
really depends on you, Nukumizu-kun.
That's why I wanted you to be vice president.
But it's still very different from
the way you two handled things.
When something's important,
she has a habit of pushing people away.
The only people she lets in are you and...
The president sure is late.
The fact that you and I are here
must mean he's alone
with Komari-chan right now.
Yeah, I guess.
Would you like one?
Don't mind if I do.
You know, I'm actually a
very cold, calculating bitch.
Okay...
I knew Komari-chan had a thing
for Shintaro way before she told him.
But I thought she'd never make a move.
I definitely underestimated her.
I was sure I'd never lose to a girl like that.
But that night at camp,
if Komari-chan hadn't been so brave,
and Shintaro and I hadn't talked things out,
everything might have
turned out differently.
After all of it, it feels like I used Komari-chan
as a stepping stone to my own happiness.
Is that why you've deliberately given
the two of them some alone time?
I-I'm done.
Did you get to talk to the prez?
I-I gave him my thanks.
Oh, good. He's been such a great guy to me
all this time. I really should thank him, too.
N-Nukumizu, you only joined
the club a little while ago.
On paper, I'm still your senpai, though.
D-Did you forget that you were a g-ghost
member and I dug you out of your grave?
Was I really dead and buried?
I-I've had so much fun in the literature club.
I'm s-so grateful to our senpai.
The p-president even thanked me.
He said it was all because of me
the club had made it this far.
That was nice of him.
Y-Yeah. But...
I-I know I'm going to start
seeing him less and less now,
and my feelings for him are going to get
weaker and weaker, and I don't want that.
Maybe it's for the best.
For the best? Why?
How should I put it?
I don't really like the phrase,
"Time heals all wounds,"
but I do think some things
need time to resolve themselves.
F-Funny coming from someone
who's never been dumped.
I kind of get it, though.
I-It's painful to hold on to something,
just waiting for it to end,
s-so I'm glad I got to let
some of my feelings out today.
W-Wait, you didn't ask him
out again, did you?
What? Th-There's no way I'd do that.
I j-just asked him if he ever liked me.
Huh?
Yeah. I asked him if Tsukinoki-senpai hadn't
been here, would he have liked me instead.
And what did he say?
H-He's always so kind.
I-I really enjoyed the time the three of us
spent together. Him, me, and Tsukinoki-senpai.
But...
Wh-When we were at camp,
I was ready to throw that all away.
S-So I told him I wasn't just trying to
make a good memory out of all of this.
B-But even then, he accepted all of me.
Even the negative parts.
I...
Episode 10
I Suppose It's a Bit Too Early for Goodbye
I'm still glad...
that I liked him.