I don't like this system at all.
Doesn't making us clean up when
the date matches our student number
let students in the 30s off the hook?
Y-Yakishio-san?
Hey, Nukumizu.
I need to talk to you about something.
Normally, this sort of thing foreshadows
a very arousing turn of events.
But in rom-com terms,
Yakishio and I are short on plot developments
that would lead to an incident
in the gym storage room.
So what happened with that thing?
Huh? What "thing" do you mean?
Oh, you know.
Mitsuki said he was gonna borrow books
from the lit club. Did he do that already?
Oh, that "thing."
I-If it's okay, I wouldn't mind
taking the books to him myself.
Okay, how about this:
Why don't we get him to pick them up
when you have a day off from your club?
My club? Why?
Um, because it'd probably be okay
for you to visit the lit club then.
As an observer or whatever.
An observer? Me?
Yeah. I mean, you could even
come to the club together then.
Both of you. Together.
Of course! Nukumizu, you're really smart!
You're actually not such a bad guy.
I had you all wrong.
I think the entire class has me all wrong.
Uh-oh.
What's wrong?
It looks like...
the door might be locked from outside.
What?!
Hey!
Somebody help!
We're still in here!
Hey!
The forecast said the temperature
was gonna get up to 35 degrees today.
It's the first really hot day of the summer.
Whoa. She must have a super fast metabolism.
Hey, Yakishio-san, you okay?
I'm fine. I'm more like an impala
than a Thomson's gazelle.
Really? You're an impala?
Basically, it's a lot faster to run on four legs.
What I'm saying is, spotted hyenas
like to get splashed with water!
She definitely doesn't sound okay!
Yakishio-san, here! It's a cooling spray!
Ooh, Nuk-kun, nice one!
Am I "Nuk-kun" now?
Spray it all over me.
Ah! Wait a second!
Hurry up.
I never thought the day would come
when a girl was begging for me!
Insta
Cool\h
Do the front next.
Insta
Cool\h
Hurry up.
Insta
Cool\h
Spray!
At this rate, I feel like...
you can't blame me if I start getting
in a weird mood. This isn't my fault!
Wait, wait, wait! Don't take it off!
Nuk-kun, what's the big deal?
It's just us girls here.
She's completely out of her mind!
This bottle still has something in it.
Wait! Y-You can't drink that!
Hey, Nuk-kun, whaddaya doing?
Y-Y-Yakishio-san! Your top! Your top!
Whoa! Something's touching me!
Something's touching me!
Hey! Is somebody in there?
Yes! Please open the door!
We're finally saved.
Catch ya when you're done.
Leave it open!
Oh, man. It's so delicious.
Heatstroke is really scary. Worst-case,
it can leave you disabled or even kill you.
Forget class, you guys.
Just rest here in the nurse's office.
And you, mister. I'll contact your homeroom
teacher. Name and class number?
I'm in your class, Sensei. It's me, Nukumizu.
Huh? You are?
Well, whatever.
Okay, Konuki-chan.
I'll let you take care of it.
Konuki-sensei, are you and
Amanatsu-sensei close friends?
We are.
We used to be classmates here and spent
a lot of time in the nurse's office together.
The stains on the ceiling
haven't changed at all since then.
I'm surprised you remember
something like that.
Well, when you get laid...
I mean, when you're leaning back,
the ceiling's right there in front of you.
This lady is kinda nuts.
You have a visitor.
Nukumizu-kun, are you okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
I brought your bento lunch. Wanna eat?
Oh, my. Am I in the way?
I'll step out for a bit, so you
can go ahead and use the room.
You can lock it from the inside.
Enjoy yourselves.
First Amanatsu-sensei, now her.
How did they even become teachers?
Omelet rice?
Yeah. I'm pretty proud of this one.
I was able to flip it and roll it nicely.
Okay, hands together.
Thank you for the food.
Oh, right. Thank you for the food.
Pretty good, right?
So how much is it worth to you, sir?
Hmm... Let's say 400 yen.
Not too shabby. But I'm gonna
step up to that 400 yen wall,
and smash through it with this!
I see. Your strategy is to add soup
to raise the assessed value.
Whatever in the world made you think...
that this is soup?
It's white sauce!
Personally speaking, I prefer ketchup,
but the extra effort does add flair!
What the heck? This is so good!
It was left over from a holiday present I got.
It's the Empire Hotel's official white sauce!
So? How much would you pay for this flavor?
For a taste of the Empire Hotel!
Five...
600 yen.
Balance
600 yen! Thank you very much!
Sounds like you guys are having fun.
Oh, Lemon-chan! Good morning.
Are you feeling better?
Much, much better.
But I don't remember what happened
at the end. How did we end up?
Huh? Um, no, uh...
A-Amanatsu-sensei rescued us.
Really?
Then I guess Amanatsu-sensei
changed my clothes for me.
Right! Amanatsu-sensei
changed your clothes.
And I didn't see a thing. Not a thing.
You'd better not have. What sort
of creep watches a girl changing?
Nukumizu-kun, that's kinda gross.
Don't say that.
I won't be able to face another day.
But anyway, what's that? It looks delicious.
I know, right? I made it myself.
Here. Say "ahh."
Why is she feeding her from my plate?
Wow, yum! What is this sauce? It's so wild!
Why, it's from the Empire Hotel!
Uh, that's actually my lunch.
The Empire Hotel?!
What's wrong, Nuk-kun?
Oh, yeah. I guess that counts
as an indirect kiss.
Mind out of the gutter, son. You're at school.
I wasn't thinking anything dirty!
Huh? Then why are you blushing?
I-I'm not!
Excuse me. Is Lemon here?
M-Mitsuki!
Are you feeling better? Here.
I brought you a get-well gift.
You brought this for me?
But you seem fine. Maybe you don't need it.
I do! I was feeling so bad,
I couldn't eat at all!
Yeah, sure looks like it.
You can't eat it if it's on your cheek.
Um, thank you.
Mitsuki-san!
Oh, Chihaya. What's up?
I was thinking of going to the study room
after class. Would you like to join me?
Oh, sorry. Gotta go home early today.
I'll see you at cram school tomorrow.
Got it. Then I'll get in touch later tonight.
Silly. I said I'll see you tomorrow.
I'd better get back to class.
Lemon, take it easy, okay?
S-Sure. Thanks.
The Complete Works
\hof Abe Kobo
of Abe Kobo
The Complete Works
Um, Tsukinoki-senpai?
Hmm?
Is it all right if I lend
some of these to a friend?
Sure, I don't mind.
Butter him up with favors,
then once he's cornered, we recruit him.
Uh-huh...
Okay, gotta go.
Shintaro keeps forgetting the
duty schedule and has to stay after.
I gotta go give him backup.
Oh, yeah. Just don't lay a finger
on the Dazai or Mishima, okay?
Shintaro? Huh. Must be her boyfriend.
Huh? What is it?
N-N-Not her boyfriend.
J-Just a ch-childhood friend.
A-And she got the order wrong.
Memo
Mishima comes first! Mishima, Dazai is the correct order!
Who the hell cares either way?
Tamaki Shintaro
See you around.
Welcome again
Let me know when you're planning to butter him up
I could almost pass for a
regular high school student.
Huh? Kaju? What are you doing here?
Big brother, have you made
any friends at school yet?
Huh? No, not yet.
I'm worried about you.
People aren't allowed to be
completely friendless after middle school.
Meaning I'm not allowed to?
For example, excluding teachers,
how many people did you talk to today?
Um... five people, I guess?
Five people?
I feel awful for hounding you so much
that you feel you have to lie to me.
Big brother, having no friends is
really nothing to be ashamed about.
But it still isn't allowed, right?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Tsuwabuki High School
Rugby Club
Congratulations on being selected
to participate in the national rugby
competition!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Tsuwabuki High School
Girls' Tennis Club
Congratulations on being selected
to participate in the national high
school tennis competition!
Nuk-kun, good morning!
O-Oh, g-good morning.
Listen, I finally remembered what happened
in the storage room yesterday.
So today, after class—
Ah! Y-You remembered what happened?
Nope! I didn't see!
I didn't see anything at all!
What? We talked about me going
to the lit club with Mitsuki today.
Huh?
Didn't you say we should come together?
Did the heat fry your brain, too?
Oh, that's right. Yeah, I totally did.
Yup, yup. Sounds good.
Okay, see you after class.
Lemon-chan sure is going after him.
Balance
Maybe I should come observe, too,
so I can back her up.
Yeah, but to the literature club?
Are you cool with that?
Heh. I really like flowers and stuff.
That's the horticulture club.
Huh?
\hLit Before
You Leap
It's Nukumizu-kun, right?
Uh, yes.
I'm Tamaki Shintaro, the club president.
So Shintaro was the president?
Very nice to meet you.
Oh, is this your Abe Kobo friend?
All Deadlines
Are Bad
Uh, actually, it isn't.
Nice to meet you. My name's Yanami,
not Abe. I've come to observe.
Really? I'm happy so many people
are interested in the lit club.
A long time ago, I tried wool felting.
Where you poke a hairball with a needle.
That's the knit club.
New club member!
Huh?
I have to go attend a presidents' meeting.
New club member!
Um, uh, President?
All Deadlines
Are Bad
Th-That sci-fi book I borrowed
was really good.
I didn't really get it, but—
You thought so?
Ah, I knew you had good taste, Komari-chan.
Whoa there.
Komari-chan, if you don't like that,
I'll tell him off myself.
I-I...
My head... d-doesn't really... uh, hate it.
You really are a cutie, Komari-chan.
You should learn from her example, Koto.
Shaddap.
See you later.
The p-president... He called...
He called me a c-cutie.
You two sure get along well.
Well, we're childhood friends.
We're kinda stuck together.
Childhood friends?
That must mean...
Homewrecker.
C-Cmon, Yanami-san.
Let's not use that talk in here.
Um—
Excuse us.
Lemon, behave yourself, okay?
Ayano. Nice timing.
This really is an outstanding collection.
Which one should I borrow?
Take whatever you like.
But if you decide to join our club, you'll be
able to borrow anything freely. Interested?
I am interested,
but I'm busy with cram school.
Oh, that's no problem. You can come
and borrow books whenever you feel like it.
And maybe your cute
girlfriend wants to join, too?
Huh? What? M-Me?
Do you mean me when you say "girlfriend"?
Oh, gosh! But I'm in the track club,
so that might be difficult.
Tsk, tsk, tsk. We're totally open
to dual memberships.
I mean, all of our members
are in other clubs, too.
Seriously? What other club am I in?
You can come hide here if you
ever want to skip track practice.
Right? And wouldn't it be nice to have
more time to spend with your girlfriend?
Huh? Would you like that, Mitsuki?
That wouldn't be fair to Lemon.
We aren't dating, anyway.
Oh? You're not?
She's always been really popular with
the guys. I wouldn't stand a chance.
Anyway, thanks for letting me borrow—
That's not true!
I don't have a boyfriend, and being popular
doesn't mean I'd go with just anyone!
O-Oh. Right.
Sorry, did I say something wrong?
Not exactly, but...
Um, I... Sorry.
What's this now?
Are you sure you two aren't dating?
You sure act like a couple.
N-No, we don't!
Huh. Are you sure?
But we aren't!
She's right. And I already have a girlfriend.
I already have a girlfriend.
Huh? What?
What's wrong, everyone?
Huh? Um, Mitsuki... You got a girlfriend?
Yeah. Just recently.
I guess I hadn't told you yet, Lemon.
Let me guess. Is it Asagumo-san?
Was it that obvious?
Well, yeah. I'll introduce
you guys properly next time.
All right, Lemon. Wanna get going?
Huh?!
Didn't you want to go
shopping together today?
No way. Is Ayano actually totally dense?
I-I've decided to join the lit club,
so I think I'll hang out here for a bit.
Oh, okay. Then I guess I'll see you later.
Was that maybe... my fault?
Yup, that was your fault.
Huh? What is it?
Gimme an application form.
Club Application
June 13th
I'd like to join the
Sex
August 1st
Name
Yaki
Huh. So Mitsuki already had a girlfriend?
What have I been doing all this time?
Running in circles, I guess.
Anyway, welcome. Wear this.
I will. I'm all worn out.
New club member!
Restaurant
Gusto
Your friend basically got dumped,
so to cheer her up,
you take her to the restaurant where you
got dumped? Do you have nerves of steel?!
Oh, uh, Yanami-san...
You're paying for yourself today, right?
Of course! But talking about money in front
of a girl who just had her heart broken...
Have you no tact at all?
Lemon-chan, we'll treat you today.
Um, you don't have to.
It's okay.
We're celebrating you joining the club, too.
All right, I'm gonna have a Hamburg steak!
Yanami-san, are you okay
eating that much before dinner?
Didn't you know?
Sweets are a diet's worst enemy.
And a Hamburg steak
before dinner is a diet's ally?
All right, I think I'll have
a bean paste sundae.
Oh my gosh!
I think I'll have that for dessert.
I thought sweets were the enemy?
Then I'll add a hamburger, too.
Can you really eat that much?
Yakishio-san, we'll take care of the bill.
Go ahead and wait for us outside.
Thank you, Nuk-kun, Yana-chan.
Okay, if it's all right with you.
Nukumizu-kun, you can be
pretty thoughtful sometimes.
You still owe me. I'm not
the one actually paying today.
You're so annoying. Fine.
But I'll tell you something, Nukumizu—
Nukumizu-kun.
Don't tell me you don't
have enough to cover it.
Is this girl seriously just completely...
Balance
stupid?
Playing
Asagumo
Yanami
Ayano
Nukumizu
You can't eat it if it's on your cheek.
Um, thank you—
That Nukumizu kid doesn't look
like much, but he's got moves.
But more importantly...
Mitsuki-san!
Oh, Chihaya. What's up?
I was thinking of going to the study room
after class. Would you like to join me?
STOP
Maybe I should set another
one up in the study room.
What are you doing here so late?
I just felt like running, I guess.
And my club didn't meet today.
You should be heading home.
I can walk you part of the way if you like.
Sensei, can I just do one more?
You want to keep running?
I feel like I'm about to get somewhere.
Yakishio
Nukumizu
All right. Go ahead and run.
But give it everything you've got.
Of course!
Episode 2
The Promised Failure for You