Wh-What are you doing here?
I was thirsty and wanted a drink of water.
So you c-came all the way out here?
Look who's talking.
You're out fountain-hopping
to avoid class, right?
Sh-Shut up. I-I came here 'cause I'm
kind of d-doing research on school water.
Research? Oh?
I'm actually quite particular
about the water here at school.
Th-Then where did you go to
drink water th-this morning?
Heh. If it's early in the day,
like first or second period,
it's gotta be west building, second floor,
next to the classroom.
At that time of day, the water in
the pipes is still from the day before.
Not only does it have less of a chlorine taste,
but it's cool in the morning, even in summer.
It's the finest drinking water.
That's...
That's weak.
What? How can you say that?
W-West building, second floor is b-best
during lunch break, just before lunch.
Lunch break, you say?
But there's no way the upper floors
are fit for use after noon.
The chlorine smell gets stronger
and the water becomes lukewarm.
A-Amateur.
W-Warm water is much gentler
on the s-stomach.
Wha... B-But the chlorine...
O-Once your nose adjusts
to the ch-chlorine smell...
"Adjusts"? Wait! You can't mean...
...i-it covers up the smell of the bathroom.
Y-You eat lunch in the bathroom?!
I wish I'd never asked.
Just eat in the club room!
Komari-chan. Nukumizu.
What are you guys doing way out here?
Oh, right. After school, I want you
both to come to the classroom.
Koto has an important announcement.
Sure.
Okay, see you later.
Literature Club
Ahem. I gathered you all
here today for one reason.
I have decided that we shall
set sail on the open net.
Absent Today
We will submit our works to the
"Become a Literary Icon" site.
Why are we suddenly doing that?
The student council got on my case
at the last club presidents' meeting.
They asked why we list composition as an
activity when we haven't written anything.
Huh? This is the literature club,
but you haven't written anything?
We say, "Write, write!"
and then don't write. That is our way.
Literature Club
If we published a zine, we'd have
to pay for paper and printing costs,
and we have no distribution channels.
That makes sense. Publishing online
is much more practical for a club.
So to that end...
This weekend, the literature club
is holding a training camp!
What?
There was an opening at the youth house
this weekend. I was able to get two rooms—
Hang on a minute!
The weekend's only two days away!
Speed equals survival in
today's publishing business.
Honestly, I want to hide in my room this weekend
You don't get it, do you?
Will you still say that
after hearing this one word?
Canned.
"Canned"? As in when an author is
confined to a hotel room to write?
Whoa!
Huh? What's with that reaction?
Haven't you always wanted to?
Doesn't it get you pumped?
Canned is cool!
All Deadlines
Are Bad
So I'd like each of you to come up
with a plot by this weekend.
Have you decided what
you're going to write, Senpai?
I'm thinking of writing an
isekai reincarnation story.
First, Mishima commits seppuku.
Then he gets reincarnated.
Dazai tries to follow by drowning himself in
the Tamagawa Aqueduct. And that's the intro.
But it's rated X, so I wouldn't be
able to show it to you... kids...
Rated X?
Ungood.
Shikiya? How long have you been there?
Tsukinoki-senpai,
a training camp requires...
a proposal... submission.
All right. I'll have the
president bring one tomorrow.
Who's that?
Sh-Shikiya from the student council.
The student council is...
always... watching you.
Shikiya, isn't the council
going a little hard on us?
No, we go after all the clubs.
Costs. Cuts. Dissolution. Annihilation.
What's wrong with this girl? At least blink!
Costs...
Tahara
City
Facility
Introduction
Ehima Outdoor Activity Center
A training camp? That sounds like fun.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
A youth facility jointly operated by the cities of Tahara
and Toyohashi. Guests can enjoy outdoor activities, sports,
and camping in a wonderful environment with a panoramic
view of Mikawa Bay.
I don't know about that. They said we'd
be "canned." It might not be much fun.
There's even a beach nearby.
I still have my swimsuit from
last year. I hope it's okay.
Huh? Wait a minute.
Are you planning to come, too?
Yesterday, on the way home,
I ran into Sosuke's mom.
We're childhood friends,
so our families are friendly, too.
Another heavy story begins.
Sosuke's mom said, "I haven't seen you in
the mornings recently. Is everything okay?"
And then, both families got the wrong idea
and thought Sosuke and I were fighting,
so they're planning to throw a "make-up"
barbecue this weekend. As a surprise.
So please, I'm begging you!
Take me to the ocean with you!
You don't need to go that far.
You could just go out for a bit instead.
Are you mocking my father's
passion for barbecuing?
He'll keep grilling for hours
and hours until I get home!
But you aren't even in the lit club—
I'll join! I'll join right this minute!
This is Yanami Anna
Pleased to meet you
Welcome to the lit club
Glad to have you
My fave canned foods are:
crab
and corned beef.
My fave canned foods are:
crab
and corned beef.
PM
Is she gonna be okay?
Can she even write a novel?
Then again, it's my first time writing, too.
What are we gonna do?
N-Nukumizu! Wh-What are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
I-Impolite!
You were impolite first.
But whatever. Adding "-san" is a pain, anyway.
Are you here to check out light novels, too?
New Comics
I-I don't know much about them,
so I thought I should study some.
You haven't decided what to write, have you?
I've actually already started writing.
Huh? Really?
M-More importantly, is Y-Yanami...
Good Night at the Late-Late-Night Café
Is Yanami joining the lit club, too?
Sounds like it. Is that a problem?
Y-Yanami's cute. Yakishio's c-cute, too.
Well, you aren't ugly, either, Komari.
Wh-What?
I mean...
P-Pretty girls never join
the l-literature club.
Hold it right there! You need to apologize
to all lit club girls everywhere!
Do it! Now!
Big brother, are you on your way home?
Yeah. You sure are late today. Shopping?
Yes. We're having curry udon today.
Big brother, I actually won't be home
this weekend. Is that all right?
Huh? I don't really care.
You won't get lonely and
start crying or anything?
I'll be fine.
I'll be away this weekend, too. I have
an overnight training camp for my club.
Huh? Does that mean
you've finally made friends?
Well, they aren't exactly friends.
Here you go, Kaju-chan.
Sir, can I also get some of your finest
red beans? I'm making red rice to celebrate.
Huh?
Did something good happen?
My brother just made his first friends ever!
Oh! That is good news!
Everyone in the shop owners' association
was worried about you!
Good
Fortune
Authorized Retailer
We thought of giving you all of our points
from the shopping arcade stamp rally,
Good
Fortune
Authorized Retailer
Good
Fortune
Authorized Retailer
Good
Fortune
Authorized Retailer
but maybe you don't need them now.
Good
Fortune
Authorized Retailer
Please don't. No, seriously!
Good
Fortune
Authorized Retailer
You sure did come through, Nukumizu.
Um, what do you mean?
What else? Yanami and Yakishio. I didn't
expect you to bring cute girls like them.
It's super rare to see our
female members in swimsuits.
What about during swim lessons?
What are you saying? School swimsuits and
personal swimsuits are two different things!
Listen. They're bound by the rules to
wear official school swimsuits in class.
But when they wear personal swimsuits,
it's because they want to.
Do you see the difference?
Please explain in more detail.
Okay, okay.
Normally, girls are too ashamed to
expose their shoulders and thighs.
But with the beach as an excuse, they willingly
walk around in what is essentially underwear.
Basically, you're allowed to stare.
No, if you don't stare,
it could be considered rude!
Do you see what I mean?
I see.
It's the magic of summer,
in a manner of speaking.
What the heck are you guys talking about?
Oh, a parasol!
And they even have beach chairs.
Thanks, Nukumizu-kun.
S-Sure.
Yana-chan, do you have sunscreen?
Yeah, I do. Hold on a sec.
I forgot it last time, and it was terrible.
Nukumizu, y-you're looking super pervy.
So, Koto, no bikini?
Okay, stop talking and let's hit the water.
Oh, I'm coming, too!
Wait up! I'll come with you!
Aren't you going in?
I-I'm good right here.
Here I come!
This is your big chance.
Why not spend time with the president?
Th-That's none of your business.
H-Hurry up and go in yourself, N-Nukumizu.
Hey, welcome back!
I have returned! It felt so good!
The ocean sure is nice.
Man, did I let loose!
You guys thirsty at all?
Oh, grab me a cola.
Were you reading this whole time?
I'd like some water.
Whoa. Yakishio-san, do you have a six-pack?
I will never forget this day
for the rest of my life.
The fact that in my youth, I've enjoyed
one day at the beach with girls in swimsuits
should sustain me for
the rest of my lonely life.
Hey, guys. What should we have for lunch?
Wanna buy something and eat it here?
How about yakisoba?
Yanami-san, aren't you
eating yakisoba right now?
I took a chance on a place that
wasn't busy, and it was a mistake.
My intuition's telling me that the shop
way down at the end is the one!
You're gonna eat another serving?
I'll go buy some, then.
Okay, thanks. Nukumizu, go with her.
Oh, uh, sure.
Hey, Yakishio-san.
Hmm?
Did you get home okay from
the restaurant the other day?
Wait, are you worried about me?
Well, I was just wondering if what I did
made you even more depressed.
You know, he can be really dense,
except when it comes to his girlfriend.
I've been hanging with him for years,
but he never saw me as a girl like that.
Yakishio-san, I, well...
Let's just have fun today.
You're right. Thanks.
What?
Okay, we're gonna run!
Hey! Wait! Hold—
Ow, ow, ow.
Nuk-kun, are you okay?
Nuk-kun, what are you doing?
Yeah, yeah. It's 'cause you
took off running, Yakishio-san.
Sorry about that. But hey, don't
be so formal. Just use my name.
Here.
What's the matter?
You know, sometimes,
girls just want to be spoiled a little.
Is that how it is?
Yana-chan was right.
You really are like that.
This is great!
Komari, don't you want any?
The p-president is reading my novel.
It's interesting. I think you write
really well. And it's a great title.
D-Do you mean it?
But you could add a subtitle to
introduce the story a little better.
H-How would I add a subtitle?
Well, let's see. If the title was
"The Literature Club Goes to the Beach,"
then maybe, "But We Didn't Realize It Was
an Enforced Nudist Beach," for example!
Or "Is it True You Get More Points
the More You Strip?" for example!
And then your view count
will go through the roof—
That's enough out of you, Shintaro!
You, too, Koto? It's not like
I was telling you to strip or any—
I said that's enough.
Hey! Please stop!
Hey, are they holding some
kind of event over there?
Let's check it out! C'mon, Komari-chan,
let's go. You've been sitting all day.
m 0 0 l 59 -1 b 55 -6 50 -11 43 -14 b 36 -17 26 -17 17 -14 b 13 -13 5 -8 -1 0
Hitani
Sea Park
Huh? N-No, I'm fine.
I wonder if they have food stands.
Oh, wow. So this is her thing.
Right? Don't you think
Komari-chan's novel is well-written?
Yes, I agree.
By the way, what sorts
of things do you write?
Me?
Well, there's this one I've had running
on Lit Icon for about three years now.
The Slave Girl I Picked Up Was
Actually an S-Rank Adventurer,
so I Decided to Become a Freeloader
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
I thought I was dead when I took a tumble down
my apartment staircase and got hit by a kei truck,
but I woke up reincarnated in another world.
I was no longer in the big city, with its hectic
morning commutes, and was now in a great forest.
With no idea which way to go, I wandered through
the forest until I stumbled upon a girl being attacked
by a monster. This chance meeting changed the course
of my life completely.
Chapter 1
A Sudden Beginning
Chapter 2
Absolute Destiny Apocalist
Light Novels in an App
Hey, I know this one. I mean, I'm reading it!
Seriously? I've never met one
of my readers in the flesh before.
I had no idea you were the Tarosuke-sensei,
whose stories have amassed over 20,000 points.
Are you gonna publish it as a book?
It's nowhere near long enough for that.
Hey!
Oof.
Giant
Fire
Sunrise
Shower
Hana-
masa
Endless Summer
Huge Volume
Here. Present for you.
Huh? Where'd you get all this?
Lemon-chan jumped into the beach
flag contest and won this as a prize.
Y-You were amazing.
Ah, please continue.
Guys, we should change
and head back to the lodge.
Okay.
Wait, Komari-chan, you haven't
gone in the water yet, have you?
Oh, uh, well...
We'll be right back!
Have fun!
Don't go too crazy!
Yakisoba
Koto, does that one look ready?
Food tastes so much better outside!
No, it's still way too soon.
I haven't had b-beef in a while.
You sure?
How was it, Komari-chan?
Didn't the water feel great?
Oh, but this one's done. Here.
I-It was salty.
Thanks.
I know, right? It feels so good!
I knew it. They're all the type...
to eat it rare without a second thought!
But I can't just stand here
waiting for time to run out.
I'm going to have to eat it raw!
Nukumizu-kun, we just put those on.
Let's wait for them to cook a bit.
Y-You're a real glutton, aren't you?
Here. If you're hungry, eat this.
Oh, thank you very much.
Someone at a nearby spot
just shared these with us.
A middle schooler, maybe?
She was so cute.
Red rice?
Immobulus! Expulso!
I'll use the last of the coals to raise
this one right. I'll name her Setsuko.
Don't you like fireworks, Yanami-san?
I wanted dessert first.
Gonna toast marshmallows?
Ta-da! Mixed organ meats!
Would ya look at that?
What are you a-doin'?
What's up?
Uh, well, look...
These are too big to do alone.
I'll do them with you.
Oh, come on. I can handle this much myself.
Look at those two.
I wish they'd hurry up and get married.
Oh, that's pretty.
Watch out, watch out!
Hey, be careful!
Oh, there's one left. I'll have that.
Ah! Setsuko!
Huh? "Setsuko"?
No, uh, I mean...
Hey, if you want it, just say so.
Here. Aah.
It's good, right?
Mm-hmm.
So how much is that worth?
Huh? Uh, um... 700?
Huh?
I'm just teasing.
Idiot! Watch out!
Komari-chan, are you hurt at all?
I-I'm okay.
President, your hand...
Don't worry about me. What would've
happened if you'd injured your face?
I-It doesn't really matter
if my face gets hurt.
Don't be stupid. Of course it matters.
Nobody looks at my face or anything, anyway.
Well, you do, right?
Do you really want to relive a bad memory
every day when you look in the mirror?
I wouldn't want that to happen.
P-President...
So don't say stuff like that.
You gotta take care of yourself. Okay?
President Tamaki...
I like you!
Here.
Komari-chan?
P-President...
I-I've always liked you.
You actually pay attention to me.
It makes me so happy.
I like you. So please...
Please go out with me!
Episode 3
Losing the Battle Before It Is Ever Fought