Please go out with me!
Well, um... this is all kind of sudden for me.
Can you give me some time to think?
Why didn't you just turn her down?
This is between me and Komari-chan.
It isn't up to you.
Oh, sure. We've never been more
than childhood friends, anyway.
Nothing but childhood friends, right?!
I just want to forget all this
and light some black snakes.
From what the president said,
it sounds like Komari might have a chance.
I never thought Tsukinoki-senpai
might end up as a losing heroine.
Whoa!
Were you in here this whole time?
I can't decide which one to go after.
Nukumizu...
Can I ask your advice?
I don't believe this guy.
That's basically like asking a worm
how to defeat a goldfish!
I confessed to Koto once,
but she turned me down.
Huh?
Are you serious? This must've been
when you were, like, four or five, right?
Why do you say that?
It was last Christmas.
That's kind of recent.
Why did she act like that after
she'd already turned me down?
It doesn't make any sense.
Judging by how she reacted,
there might be some misunderstanding.
First of all, you should go back
and have a good talk with her.
Are you...
Are you actually really
experienced in love?
Why would you think that?
Try swallowing first.
Tsukinoki-senpai took her things and left!
Where's she gonna go this late?
I have no idea.
Koto.
I thought you turned me down
when I asked you out last Christmas.
Huh? Turned you down? Me?
You know. By that tree at the station.
You said, "Yeah, in your dreams."
I think you said, "If you can't find someone to
marry you, I guess I could fill in, so don't worry."
Is that when?
That's what the president meant by a
"confession"? That's worse that I imagined!
On Christmas? Is that how you ask
someone out on Christmas? In high school?
Are you completely brain dead?!
I've been waiting...
All this time, I've been waiting for you.
Waiting and waiting.
Koto, I'm sorry.
Let's go, Yanami-san.
Huh? But it's just starting to get good.
Hey. Nukumizu-kun?
Could you—
We gotta go.
Um...
We need to give them some space.
Huh? What is it?
I mean, uh, my hand?
Are you ever gonna let go of it?
O-Oh, sorry! I-I-I didn't mean anything by it.
I'm really sorry.
You don't need to apologize that much.
What's this, Nukumizu-kun?
Do you have something to confess to me?
N-No, I don't.
Fine with me. Go right ahead.
I'll turn you down, though.
I just said I don't!
Oh? Nuk-kun, what are you doing out here?
What are you doing, Yakishio?
Looking for stag beetles.
I want to give one to
Komari-chan to cheer her up.
What makes you think a
beetle will cheer her up?
Check this one out. It's huge!
It's in your hands now, Nuk-kun.
I-I just talked to the president.
H-He said no. Formally turned me down.
He did, huh? He actually
gave you a straight answer?
N-Nukumizu, I bet you would've
chickened out and made me wait.
How did you guess?
Y-You really are a jerk.
The president actually thought about it.
He seriously considered
g-going out with me.
For just a second,
I had Tsukinoki-senpai beat.
I'm gonna cry. C-Can you leave me alone?
Please?
Until recently, I'd never
even talked to these people.
Now that we're here together,
I'm getting caught up in all their drama.
What's gonna happen after camp ends?
Maybe I'll try writing something.
Become a
Literary Icon
All right, I'm submitting the first parts.
Komari-chan, is yours good like this?
Yes, with that title.
I don't want to split it up.
I want people to read part one like this.
Good idea. That way, people
can see the quality of your writing.
Okay, upload complete.
P-President, I don't really know
how to use the Lit Icon site,
so I hope you'll keep showing me how.
Sure. No problem.
S-Senpai, I-I just uploaded my story,
so please take a look.
Sure. I'll leave a comment.
U-Um...
And please keep coming to the club.
I-It'd be lonely without you.
What? Oh, gosh. Sorry, I don't mean to... Huh?
S-Senpai, you d-don't have
to worry about me. So...
Please don't cry. It's okay.
Thanks.
Hey, did you see that yesterday?
I did, I did!
Good morning, Nuk-kun!
Oh. Good morning.
I have a draft for the literature club.
What is this? A picture diary?
Yeah. Think you could upload
it to that site for me?
Wait, is that supposed to be me?
Did you upload yours, Nuk-kun?
Uh, yeah. Just the beginning, though.
Oh, hey, you've already got comments!
Anyway, please upload mine
when you get a chance.
Uh, sure.
AM
Halfwit on Love St.
Save
Confirm
Settings
My childhood friend, Sakura Misuzu, was wearing the uniform of Harukita
High School. I sneaked up on her to make fun of her, but she teased me first.
Did you hear? Yanami's been
hanging around a new guy recently.
Seriously?
Who?
You know, that guy from our class. Um...
Nukumizu?
Oh, the name rings a bell.
School Council
Announcements
But Yanami's pretty popular, right?
Isn't she out of his league?
For sure.
Yanami's got bad taste.
Yeah.
I don't even know what he looks like, though.
So what are they to each other, anyway?
Who knows?
I guess I don't really get Yanami, either.
No kidding.
Let's go.
That was pretty rude, Nukumizu-kun.
Huh?
You totally ignored me.
Well, I wasn't trying to.
Huh. I guess that's okay, then.
Cucumber and, uh, what's this? Moromi miso?
Yeah. What's it worth to you?
What's the matter?
It's worth 2,867 yen.
Oh! That's a new record...
Wait. Isn't that about the same
as the remaining balance?
It feels like I've been taking advantage
of you this whole time, Yanami-san.
I don't think that's right.
The bentos were really good, though.
Thanks for everything.
This did all start because I didn't have
enough money, but I'm enjoying it now.
I don't want to call it off just like that.
People have been spreading rumors
about us eating lunch together.
You don't want that, do you?
People thinking that we might be—
Listen. I don't know
where you're going with this.
Did I do something to hurt your feelings?
No!
No, you didn't.
But I just don't like it.
I don't want people spreading
rumors like that about us.
Okay, fine.
That's fine with me.
I won't talk to you anymore.
Thanks for everything.
It was kind of fun. Bye.
You seem sorta out of it.
No need to worry. I'm always out of it.
Oh? Or maybe you have someone on your mind?
Not that it's any of my business.
But you'll regret it if you don't go talk to her.
Just some friendly advice from your senpai.
You are
the pen!!
So you were here.
I just came to return a book.
Yanami-san, got a minute?
What is it? My friends are waiting
for me, so keep it short.
After eating lunch together
for all this time,
I think I actually started
looking forward to it.
So...
So?
I had fun, too. I just wanted you to know.
Oh. Okay. Well, I'm going now.
Komari?
Yanami d-dumped you, huh?
I-I just came here to s-say,
"Serves you right."
Yanami-san and I weren't like that, though.
You th-thought you could be happy
while we suffered. Y-You've got some nerve.
Dumped, huh?
I guess from the outside, it might have
looked like we were in a relationship.
PET Bottles
Cans
But it wasn't like that at all. It was...
Hey, are you ready?
We're coming!
What actually was it, anyway?
Wait up!
Nukumizu.
Hakamada.
I've been looking for you.
Yo.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
I know how this goes.
What's the wallet for?
I was wrong. I misread the situation.
You always were a joker, Nukumizu.
You've been seeing Anna recently, right?
Huh?
A couple was spotted fooling
around by the old building.
Everyone's talking about it.
No, it's not like that!
That makes me so happy, man.
No, listen...
If Anna has a guy she likes now,
I want to give her my support.
So please take good care of her—
You've got it all wrong!
You know Yanami-san always
liked you, right, Hakamada?
Well, I guess...
Yanami-san and I aren't like that at all!
She's still totally into you!
Now, what are we all talking about, I wonder?
Anna?
Komari-chan messaged me saying Nukumizu-kun
was getting bullied by some stud.
Sorry, Anna. I just really hoped
you'd find someone new.
Would you cut that out?
I just want you to be happy.
Stop.
I know there are way better
guys than me out there.
I said stop!
Anna!
Would you just stop?!
Listen, Hakamada.
I don't care that you turned her down.
Pick up and dump all the girls
you want. I don't care.
But you can't tell Yanami-san
how she's supposed to feel.
If you do, she's gonna forget about how much
she used to like you. Don't you get that?
You want her to be happy?
To find someone new?
You're the one who turned her down!
You're the last person
who should be saying that!
Hey! You okay?
You're right. You're absolutely right.
Okay. Sorry I got so pushy there.
"Turned her down"? "Turned her down"?! Shut up!
Why are you pretending
like this is some happy ending?!
Sosuke!
I always liked you, Sosuke.
And I still like you! I'm not over you at all!
Anna, I'm sorry—
No! Don't apologize!
Whoever I fall for next
is none of your business.
Because I still really, really like you.
So go and be happy with Himemiya Karen.
Go and be happy without me!
I'm gonna keep liking you if I want.
I'll find someone else when I'm ready!
Hey! Ow!
Uh, and I'm getting beaten up because...
There's no reason!
You should both feel bad. Sosuke,
you need to say sorry to Nukumizu-kun.
O-Oh, right.
My bad, Nukumizu.
I shouldn't have dragged you into this.
No, no, it's okay.
You, too, Nukumizu-kun.
You need to say sorry to me.
Well?
I'm sorry. I'll try to be
more considerate next time.
Good. I forgive you.
How are conversations like this
supposed to end, anyway?
That's a good question.
Did everyone get their report cards?
Summer
vacation is:
Byzantine!!
All right, then, ya dorks!
Summer vacation is on!
Balance
Remaining
Yen
AM
File List
No Title
Draft 1
Light Novels Purchased
Important Notes
Draft 1
AM
File List
No Title
Draft 1
Light Novels Purchased
Important Notes
Draft 1
AM
File List
No Title
Draft 1
Light Novels Purchased
Important Notes
Draft 1
Light Novels Purchased
Important Notes
Draft 1
AM
File List
No Title
Draft 1
AM
File List
No Title
Draft 1
Light Novels Purchased
Important Notes
Draft 1
N-Nukumizu.
Did that guy take your money yesterday?
Of course not.
Th-Then...
Did he take you?!
Don't get so hot and bothered!
Hey, Yana-chan, this is bad!
They're totally getting in the mood.
I don't know for sure, but I kinda doubt it.
This is Nukumizu-kun, after all.
Oh? Did we actually interrupt something?
D-Don't be stupid.
Is the lit club doing
anything during vacation?
Um, Tsukinoki-senpai did say she
wanted to do something together.
Awesome! It's summer, so let's go hunt beetles!
The training camp was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
Hmm? What is it?
Oh, uh, well...
I'll tell you later.
U-Um...
I-I'm thinking about maybe
starting running or s-something.
W-Will you teach me good form and stuff—
I've got you! Let's train to run the
100-meter in under 12 seconds together!
N-Nukumizu!
Y-You owe me one! W-Wait up...
Kinda weird, isn't it?
I mean, I never really crossed paths
with you or Komari-chan before.
And I didn't really know what the lit club
did until we went camping together.
But when I tried writing, I really enjoyed it.
And I liked the books
Komari-chan recommended.
I think books are great.
What's the matter?
Yanami-san, we need to talk.
Huh? We do?
Yeah. About something really important.
Now wait just a second!
Nukumizu-kun, you should probably think
this through carefully one more time.
I've thought about it enough.
If I don't say it right now, I know I'll regret it.
U-Um, okay.
I'll just listen, then.
Yanami-san, will you...
Y-Yes?
...please become friends with me?
Sorry! I think of you as a friend!
Become friends?
Yeah.
That's all you meant?
Hold on a sec.
I didn't even ask you out and
you already turned me down?!
Well, yeah, I guess you could say I did.
Welcome to the land of the dumped.
I wasn't dumped! I didn't ask you out!
If I was going to ask you out, first we'd
have to be friends for two or three years,
then once we'd confirmed our feelings
for each other, we could, um...
Does that mean you're going to propose
to me in three years, Nukumizu-kun?
Should I save you the trouble and say "no" now?
No, I'm not! I mean, that's different!
We're just friends anyway, aren't we?
Huh? Are we?
What else would we be?
That's what I'm talking about, Nukumizu-kun.
What is what you're
talking about, Yanami-san?
Thanks, Yanami-san.
You're very welcome.
Nice to befriend you, fellow dumpee.
I still haven't been dumped, though.
Episode 4
When You Stare into a Losing Heroine,
the Losing Heroine Stares Back into You