"Anyone Who Says I'm Flat-Chested
Needs to Step in a Pile of Dog Poop."
I've waited so long for this to come out.
Summer vacation's almost over,
so I wanna get home and enjoy what's left
of it reading in an air-conditioned room.
Welcome home, big brother!
We have a situation!
What's wrong, Kaju? Why are you so upset?
It's an emergency! We need to
schedule an interview immediately!
O-Or should we just conduct one right now?
All right. Take a deep breath.
Once you've calmed down,
tell me what happened.
Okay! I have calmed down!
She showed up without warning
while I was preparing lunch!
Oh! Lunch today is
leftover curry from yesterday!
Yeah, she hasn't calmed down at all.
Well, at least I know what's for... lunch...
It can't be.
Oh, Nukumizu-kun! Long time no see!
This curry is so good. Don't they say
curry tastes better on the second day?
Um, Yanami-san, why are you
in my house eating curry?
Don't talk with your mouth full!
Well, I've been visiting all my friends
to give them somen noodles.
Grandmother's
\h\hThreads
Highest Quality
Grandmother's
\h\hThreads
Highest Quality
Why do you have so much somen?
Dad's salary was paid in somen this month.
His salary? What's going on?
Some stuff happened, and he
got all of his July pay in somen.
So we have tons of somen at home.
Like, a street value of 300,000 yen.
"Somen" isn't some codeword, is it?
Is this stuff legal?
Grandmother's
\h\h\h\h\hThreads
Of course it is! What kind of family
do you think I'm from, exactly?
And I've eaten it. A lifetime's worth.
I don't really get it, but I think I got it.
Want some more curry?
That was my third plate. I'm good now.
You weren't on your second?
Um, Yanami-san. Would you mind
if I asked you a few things?
Start Recording
Recording
First of all, your date of birth and blood type.
Your family structure, hobbies, and skills.
And when did you start seeing my big brother?
Hey, look. Yanami-san's really busy.
Can't you save this for another time?
But dear brother, I need her to
tell me stories about your school.
Nukumizu-kun, you make
her call you "dear brother"?
I don't make her call me that!
There's a difference!
Comfortably lukewarm with
just the perfect whiff of chlorine.
The tap water during summer
vacation is something special.
Uh, is that you, Shikiya-senpai?
And you must be... the boy
from the literature club?
Um...
What's she doing here?
I came for something to drink,
but I ran out of energy.
Here you go.
Tip it for me.
What? Huh?
Hurry up.
What in the world am I doing here?
Thanks.
Brought me back to life.
By the way...
I heard Koto-san and Tamaki-san
started dating. Is it true?
Huh? Uh, yes. It is.
Oh, it is?
Man, she's scary!
Absent Today
Okay, should we get down to business?
We actually got a notice
from the student council.
The student council?
All clubs are required to report
their activities over summer vacation.
That's what I wanted to
talk to you all about today.
But summer vacation's almost over. Why now?
Why now? Well...
We don't have a choice. I was busy
with driving school and forgot all about it.
What about entrance exams?
So here's my idea:
we take the web novels we wrote before
and make them into a book. How's that sound?
Here's a sample.
m 420 20 l 610 20 610 80 420 80
Is It More Painful
to Be the Person
Who Waits
or the Person
Who Sleeps Alone?
(All Ages)
What kind of sample is that?
Okay! I'll write the next part
of the one I wrote at camp.
What will you write, Komari-chan?
A new work
A new work?
You sure go all-out, Komari-chan.
You, Nukumizu-kun?
Huh?
Well, I guess I could revise the first part
of Halfwit on Love St. and submit that.
Good. That settles it.
Okay, when you finish your
manuscript, send it to me.
Also, once we're done here,
can someone go help out in the library?
Help out with what?
Every year, a club member helps the
library with collection maintenance.
In exchange, they let us put in requests
when they order new books.
Yeah, it's a "we scratch their back,
they scratch ours" sort of thing.
Don't you have a middle school
reunion party later?
Wait, is Hakamada going?
Of course. Karen-chan's coming, too.
Even though Himemiya-san
was an exchange student?
Among my friends, if we start dating someone,
we have to introduce them to everyone.
Are you gonna be okay there?
Don't worry. I'm no longer the
same person I was in the first term.
Yes, today I am full of gratitude for all things
in the world around me, great and small.
I have opened my heart to kindness.
Excuse me?
Shall I explain it in words even you
can understand, Nukumizu-kun?
I won't get my hopes up, but sure.
Well, you see, Sosuke and Karen-chan
are both dear friends of mine.
And when my dear friends find happiness,
shouldn't that delight me, as well?
Essentially, by going out together,
those two have blessed me with great joy.
At this stage, I feel nothing
but gratitude toward them.
If you say so, Yanami-san.
You should read this as well, Nukumizu-kun.
Magic Words
to Lighten
Your Heart
Umashima San
Uh, what is that book?
Well, you see, it teaches you
how to accept yourself.
You don't have to take
the yakitori off the stick.
You can eat the whole thing at once.
That's the sort of wisdom contained within.
Right. So it's a self-help book
you read when you've lost it.
Nukumizu!
Are you on duty today?
Oh, uh, yeah.
Oh, does this stand out?
Huh? Well, kinda.
It was a present from Chihaya.
She told me never to take it off.
Like, come on, right?
When she gave it to me, she made it
this big surprise. You know what it's like.
Sure.
I guess that's what they call
"humble-bragging."
Still, everyone around me is getting dumped,
so it was kind of a breath of fresh air.
Wh-What?
Nothing. Oh, Komari, you said you'd write
something new. What are you gonna write?
A r-reincarnation isekai. R-Romance genre.
I-I actually started it
during summer vacation.
Seriously?
Tsuwabuki High School
Library
Class
Collection
I-I even uploaded it to Lit Icon.
Guts Justice
(Battle)
Silent Tonic
Matsushita Shinji
(Suspense)
Forty-Six
Handler Fight
(Robots)
(Comedy)
Let the Broken
Engagement Ring Out!
Kuon Usagi
(Romance)
Violet Operation
Hyakushiki Kenjiro
Mikado-sama: Love Is Warned – Carnal Romance
Oda Shimajiro
(Romance)
Personal
Master Velvet
(Suspense)
Motakoi: Love Is DIFFICULT for Otaku
(Comedy)
That's your pen name?
Wait, eighth place overall?!
Every time I refresh, I have more points!
When did you find the time?
Yakishio Lemon
Finished practice. Sorry I couldn't make it
to lit club. I have plans today,
so let's run another time.
Total Rating
Rating PT Average
Rating PT Total
Number of Ratings
Bookmarks
Likes
Comments
Review
Access
Overview
Edit
Product Settlings
Product Title
Let the Broken
Engagement Ring Out!
Author Name
Kuon Usagi
K
Finished practice. Sorry I couldn't make it
to lit club.\h\h\h
\hI have plans today,
so let's run another time.
M-Message from Yakishio.
You've been messaging her?
W-We've been going running
together now and then.
Oh, yeah. I remember you talking about that.
Tsuwabuki High School
Library
Class
Collection
I-It's all your fault, Nukumizu.
Well, I apologize.
But if you don't want to go,
why not just say no?
Wh-When someone comes on to me
really hard, I-I can never say no.
You've got a personality that's straight
out of a dirty comic. I need all the details.
Uh, no, what I mean is,
do you want me to talk to Yakishio for you?
A-Actually, I kinda like it.
Sh-She lets me set the pace,
and carries me piggyback when I'm tired.
D-Does Yakishio have a-any brothers?
Huh? Oh, I have no idea. Why do you ask?
Recently, Yakishio has...
No, never mind.
You are
\h\hthe pen!!
What? Oh it's you, Nuk-kun.
Y-Yakishio! At least lock the door!
I'm wearing stuff underneath.
You're overreacting, Nuk-kun.
So that's how she ties the ribbon.
The track club room's too cramped,
so I'm really glad they let me change here.
You take your hair clip out for practice, huh?
No, I always leave it in.
But I polished it yesterday
and didn't want it to get dirty.
Is something up?
Huh? What? No, nothing.
See you later.
Was Yanami-san with you
at your club yesterday?
Huh? Yeah, she was.
That's wonderful.
When you said you made a friend recently,
that was Yanami-san, wasn't it?
Well, yeah.
What do you say to inviting her over again?
I simply must give her a proper interview!
You don't need to interview her.
But she's just a friend.
It isn't that big a deal.
It's not like we hang out alon—
But that's how it always begins!
When I saw her up close,
she was a lovely person!
Big brother, is that from Yanami-san?
Um, it might be.
She's asking you out to tea!
Going to a café with a girl...
That's practically a date!
No, it really isn't.
You awake? If you have time, wanna
get something to drink?
Sure
That's what I told Kaju, anyway. But going
to a café with a girl during vacation...
Is that not what one would call a date?
In all the light novels
and manga I've read,
even if you aren't going out,
it counts as a date.
Which means that Yanami...
has asked me out on a date?!
This world should perish.
Yup, this definitely isn't a date.
I knew this would happen.
I knew this was how it would turn out.
But to see it happening before my eyes...
You mean when you see them
flirting and stuff?
No, they don't do a lot of
flirting and stuff in public.
Isn't that a good thing?
That isn't the issue!
She quietly cleans up after they eat,
and he carries her bag
for her like it's nothing.
It's that casual chemistry between them!
When they meet,
they communicate with just a look.
They share reward cards.
Their ringtones are the same.
And then, they walk home together
without saying anything first!
Damn straight! They're like newlyweds in heat
who can't keep their paws off each other!
Would...
What?!
Would you like anything else?
No! We're fine!
Ooh, nice. Very nice.
Yanami-san, you're just having a
cream soda today? You're not eating?
Nukumizu-kun, listen closely.
Somen noodles are carbohydrates.
They're essentially sugar.
Yeah, I know.
But those little guys are all cool
and slippery, and they look so thin.
Doesn't it seem like they'd be okay to eat?
Um, so you're saying you ate too
much somen and gained wei—
No, I have not gained weight!
But a cream soda is also mostly sugar.
Drinks don't count! There's a theory
that ice cream doesn't make you fat.
They're dropping hints.
Huh? What's that mean?
Nukumizu-kun, I want to
drop hints like that, too.
I'll spread posts all around social media
hinting that I'm with a boy
to distract them and stuff.
What's the point of that?
Huh?
It's Ayano and Yakishio.
What are they doing together?
Nukumizu-kun, do you think they're cheating?
But they've been friends a long time.
They're cheating.
But like, if you and Hakamada went somewhere
together, that wouldn't be cheating, would it?
It's cheating!
Looks like they already left.
Well, maybe we should call it
for today. I'll see you later.
You're giving up already?
Hey, Nukumizu-kun. Do you know that girl?
Hello there. Do you remember who I am?
Um...
It's me, Asagumo Chihaya!
Oh, Ayano's girlfriend, right?
Yes! Did you happen to see Mitsuki-san
and Yakishio-san come this way?
Yeah, they were—
G-Gosh, I really couldn't say.
So you did see them.
Uh, see them? Well, yes, but...
Shall we... find somewhere
more comfortable to talk?
Why does it have to be my room?
Is this poster made out of cloth?
You mustn't ask that, Yanami-san.
It is polite to pretend not
to notice things like that.
Oh, so this is the kind of poster you'd
be embarrassed to show other people?
If a girl from class saw I had a tapestry
full of beautiful girls in underwear,
I don't know how I'd live with myself.
Hold on! That isn't underwear!
They're combat uniforms!
If they're combat uniforms,
why are they showing so much skin?
That's because they release
mana from their skin...
for the, uh, Sigma Drive.
Oh, I see. So why are the girls
crawling on top of each other in bed?
Someone put me out of my misery!
When the five Awakened join together,
the Sigma Drive begins to resonate,
and that allows the legendary weapon,
Pashupatastra, to be unsealed.
So you see, there is a valid reason
for these girls in combat uniforms
to be physically connected.
She just kind of spoiled it.
I haven't read that far yet.
I've brought drinks for everyone.
I apologize for visiting unannounced.
Woohoo! Thanks!
So what did you want to talk about?
Yes, of course. I would like to
be completely honest with you.
I suspect Mitsuki-san is cheating on me.
I have been following him
to try to catch him in the act.
So if possible, I would like to ask
you two for your assistance.
Sorry, but—
I guess I don't really mind assisting.
Yanami-san?!
I am aware that those two were
childhood friends. And I am aware that...
she has a crush on Mitsuki-san.
Black Thunder
I like Mitsuki-san very much.
That's why I want him to be happy.
Even if that means he
doesn't remain by my side.
Are you saying...
I've been wondering for quite some time...
if maybe he should've dated her instead.
It may look like I came out of nowhere
and stole Mitsuki-san from her.
That's why I want to ascertain
Mitsuki-san's true feelings.
If he truly does have feelings
for Yakishio-san, then I'm...
prepared to step aside.
It feels like my brother
is going very far away.
If it comes to that, Nuku-chan,
I'll take you as my own.
But I want my brother.
Nuku-chan, you're such a cutie.
C'mon and be my bride already.
I don't wanna.
Please come to Toyohashi Station
Asagumo Chihaya
Why did you decide to help her, Yanami-san?
Did you see the look on Lemon-chan's face
when she was walking with Ayano-kun?
You wouldn't look like that with
someone you've really given up on.
When push comes to shove, the only people
who can really watch over Lemon-chan,
or really chew her out,
are you and me, right?
Are he and Lemon-chan here?
Yes. They appear to be visiting
the food carts one by one.
We should wait here.
How did you know they'd be meeting here?
With GPS.
She said that like it was nothing!
So then—
Voices down! They're here!
At the Italian gelato shop.
Paperback Book Cover
Asagumo-san?
What a lovely book cover.
Don't you think he'd love it?
Yeah, that's nice. He does love books.
Mitsuki-san says he wants to find
a job that has to do with books.
The first time he told me that,
I was quite surprised.
I realized someone who shared my dream
was standing right beside me.
You know, he really dislikes sweet things.
I was aware of that, so I've never
suggested anything like that.
So I've never gone out to eat anything
sweet with him, like gelato.
Uh, okay... but hey, what about savory crêpes?
And the gelato Ayano was eating may not
have been a sweet one. Like, uh, tuna mayo?
Tuna mayo by itself would
give him an upset stomach.
Mitsuki-san would need
something like a salad.
I envy Yakishio-san. She's straightforward
and expresses her feelings clearly.
All I ever think about is how
I don't want to upset Mitsuki-san.
I'm sure it's fine if you want to
eat ice cream together sometimes.
He isn't the type to get upset
over a request like that.
You're actually a very kind person,
Nukumizu-san. I had you all wrong.
I think the entire school has me all wrong.
This way!
H-Hey, wait!
Ayano? Wasn't Yakishio with him?
It was only Mitsuki-san.
I'll check out the situation outside.
Nukumizu-san, I deeply
regret to inform you...
Yes?
Mitsuki-san has found us.
Why are you guys here together?
U-Um...
Mitsuki-san.
I would like to suggest that...
Nukumizu-san explains it all to you.
Episode 5
Asagumo Chihaya Is Led Astray